getsomeheadspace.com 2011-12-17

# Headspace : Meditation and Mindfulness. Meditate, be mindful. Learn How To Meditate with Headspace.

## headspace meditation limited   
company no. 07094561 trading as ‘headspace’

("we") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. this policy and any other documents referred to on it sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.  
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is_headspace meditation limited company no. 07094561.

## Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.getsomeheadspace.com (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Headspace Meditation Limited, and when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.
  * Voting & Facebook profile information

## IP addresses and cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

## Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things,  the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Athough we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

## Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Headspace Meditation Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Headspace Meditation Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info@getsomeheadspace.com.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@getsomeheadspace.com.

**Terms and conditions for the supply of services - consumers  
Headspace Meditation Limited  
company no. 07094561 trading as ‘Headspace’**

  1. ## Agreed terms for consumers

This page contains the terms and conditions on which we supply meditation courses or other courses/services listed on www.getsomeheadspace.com ('website') to you. Please read these terms carefully before ordering any meditation or other courses/services from our website. When you order a meditation course or other courses/services from our website, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions.

You will be asked to click "I accept" at the appropriate place prior to your purchase. If you do not click "I accept", you will not be able to complete your purchase.

    * 1.1 **Basis of sale**
      * (a) We consider these Terms and the Order to set out the whole agreement between you and us for the supply of the Services. These Terms only apply to our contracts with consumers.
      * (b) Please check that the details in these Terms and on the Order are complete and accurate before you commit yourself to the contract. If you think that there is a mistake, please make sure that you ask us to confirm any changes in writing, as we only accept responsibility for statements and representations made in writing by our authorised employees and agents.
      * (c) Please ensure that you read and understand these Terms before you submit the Order, because you will be bound by the Terms once a contract comes into existence between us, in accordance with clause 1.4.
    * 1.1 Any samples, drawings, descriptions or advertising we issue, and any descriptions or illustrations contained in our catalogues or brochures, are issued or published solely to provide you with an approximate idea of the Services they describe. They do not form part of the contract between you and us or any other contract between you and us for the supply of the Services.
    * 1.2 If any of these Terms are inconsistent with any term of the Order, the Order shall prevail.
    * 1.3 The Order is an offer by you to enter into a binding contract with us, which we are free to accept or decline at our absolute discretion.
    * 1.4 These Terms shall become binding on you and us when: 
      * 1.4.1 we issue you with written acceptance of an Order with your email invite; or
      * 1.4.2 we notify you that we are able to provide the Services, whichever is the earlier, at which point a contract shall come into existence between us.
    * 1.5 Any quotation for the Services is given on the basis that a binding contract shall only come into existence in accordance with clause 1.4 A quotation from us shall be valid for a period of 30 calendar days from its date of issue, unless we notify you in writing that we have withdrawn it during this period.
    * 1.6 We shall confirm your order and assign you with an email invitation. Please quote the order number in all subsequent correspondence with us.
    * 1.7 You may at any time before any agreed delivery date amend or cancel an Order by providing us with written notice to info@getsomeheadspace.com . If you amend or cancel an Order:, your liability to us shall be limited to payment to us of all costs we reasonably incur in fulfilling the Order until we receive your amendment or cancellation. However, where the amendment or cancellation is due to our failure to comply with these Terms you shall have no liability to us for it.
    * 1.8 If you cancel more than 2 weeks before the commencement date of the Services as set out in your Order then we will attempt to accommodate you on another course or we may offer you a full refund. If you cancel less than 2 weeks before the commencement date then we will accommodate you on another course. If you do not turn up at the course according to your Order at all then you forfeit your right to be accommodated on another course or a refund.
    * 1.9 We have the right to revise and amend these Terms from time to time to reflect changes in market conditions affecting our business, changes in technology, changes in payment methods, changes in relevant laws and regulatory requirements and changes in our system's capabilities. You will be subject to the policies and terms in force at the time that you order the Services from us, unless any change to those policies or these Terms is required by law or government or regulatory authority in which case it will apply to orders you have previously placed that we have not yet fulfilled. If the services are ongoing, we will give you prior notice of any changes to these Terms and you can choose to cancel the Order without penalty before the new Terms affect you.
  2. ## Quality of services

    * 2.1 Unless we are prevented from doing so by a Force Majeure Event, we will provide Services which: 
      * 2.1.1 conform in all material respects with their description;
      * 2.1.2 are carried out with reasonable care and skill;
      * 2.1.3 are fit for any purpose we say the Services are fit for, or for any purpose for which you use the Services and about which you have informed us, or we could reasonably expect you to use the Services;
      * 2.1.4 are free from material defects in design, material and workmanship; and
      * 2.1.5 comply with all applicable statutory and regulatory requirements for supplying the Services in the United Kingdom.
    * 2.2 This warranty is in addition to your legal rights in relation to Services which are not carried out with reasonable skill and care or which otherwise do not conform with these Terms. Advice about your legal rights is available from your local Citizens' Advice Bureau or Trading Standards office.
    * 2.3 These Terms apply to any replacement Services we supply to you in the unlikely event that the original Services do not conform with these Terms.
    * 2.4 You must provide us, in sufficient time, with any information and instructions relating to the Services that is or are necessary to enable us to provide the Services in accordance with these Terms.
    * 2.5 If you do not, or you provide us with incomplete, incorrect or inaccurate information or instructions, we may cancel the Order by giving you written notice, or we may make an additional charge of a reasonable sum to cover any extra work that is required.
    * 2.6 We only supply the Services for domestic and private use, and you agree not to use the Services for any commercial purpose.
  3. ## Provision of services

    * 3.1 We will supply the Services to you from or on a specific date or the date set out in the Order.
    * 3.2 The Services will be supplied for a period as stated in the Order or until otherwise terminated in accordance with these Terms.
    * 3.3 We will make every effort to complete the Services on time but there may be delays due to circumstances beyond our control. In this case we will complete the Services as soon as reasonably possible.
    * 3.4 We may have to suspend the Services if we have to deal with technical problems, or to make improvements to the Service. We will let you know in advance where this occurs, unless the problem is urgent or an emergency.
  4. ## Defective services

    * 4.1 In the unlikely event that the Services do not conform with these Terms, please let us know as soon as possible after we have carried them out. We will: 
      * 4.1.1 provide you with a full or partial refund depending on what is reasonable; or
      * 4.1.2 re-perform the Services and offer you another date.
    * 4.2 These Terms will apply to any replacement Services we supply to you.
  5. ## Intellectual property rights

    * 5.1 The copyright, design right and all other intellectual property rights in any materials and other documents or items that we prepare or produce for you in connection with the Services will belong to us absolutely.
    * 5.2 You may not use the materials, documents or other items provided to you by us for any commercial purpose.
  6. ## Price and payment

    * 6.1 The price of the Services will be as set out in the quotation we provided to you or, if we have not provided a quotation or the quotation has expired, in our price list in force at the time we confirm your Order. Prices are liable to change at any time, but price changes will not affect Orders that we have confirmed in writing.
    * 6.2 These prices include VAT. However, if the rate of VAT changes between the date of the Order and the date of delivery, we will adjust the VAT you pay, unless you have already paid for the Services in full before the change in the rate of VAT takes effect.
    * 6.3 We may ask for upfront payment by Paypal upon their terms and conditions or invoice you for the Services in advance when you place your order OR at any time after we have provided the Services to you OR monthly or in some other period in advance. The invoice will quote the Order Number. You must pay the invoice in cleared monies when you book the Services online using the payment methods detailed on the website.
    * 6.4 If you do not make any payment due to us by the due date for payment, we may charge interest to you on the overdue amount at the rate of 4% a year above the base lending rate of Barclays Bank Plc from time to time. This interest shall accrue on a daily basis from the due date until the date of actual payment of the overdue amount, whether before or after judgment. You must pay us interest together with the overdue amount.
    * 6.5 Without limiting any other remedies or rights that we may have, if you do not pay us on time, we may cancel or suspend our performance of the Services or any other outstanding Order until you have paid the outstanding amounts.
  7. ## Limitation of liability

    * 7.1 Subject to clause 8.2, if either of us fails to comply with these Terms, neither of us shall be responsible for any losses that the other suffers as a result, except for those losses which we or you could reasonably foresee would result from the failure to comply with these Terms.
    * 7.2 Neither of us shall be responsible for losses that result from our failure to comply with these Terms including, but not limited to, losses that fall into the following categories: 
      * 7.2.1 loss of income or revenue;
      * 7.2.2 loss of business;
      * 7.2.3 loss of anticipated savings; or
      * 7.2.4 loss of data.
      * 7.3 This clause does not include or limit in any way our liability for:
      * 7.3.1 death or personal injury caused by our negligence; or
      * 7.3.2 fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; or
      * 7.3.3 any breach of the obligations implied by section 12 of the Sale of Goods Act 1979 or section 2 of the Supply of Services and Services Act 1982; or
      * 7.3.4 losses for which it is prohibited by section 7 of the Consumer Protection Act 1987 to limit liability; or
      * 7.3.5 any other matter for which it would be illegal or unlawful for us to exclude or attempt to exclude our liability.
  8. ## Events outside our control

    * 8.1 Due to the unique nature of the Services contained within an Order that they must be performed by a limited number of highly qualified instructors we will not be liable or responsible for any failure to perform the Services contained in an Order due to sickness of the instructors, or any events that may lead to our instructors having to cancel the event. If this shall occur then we will endeavour to inform you as soon as possible by email within a reasonable time period that the Order is cancelled and we will offer you another date or if you are unable to attend another date, we will offer a refund.
    * 8.2 We will not in any case be responsible for a delay in performance of, any of our obligations under these Terms that is caused by events outside our reasonable control (Force Majeure Event).
    * 8.3 A Force Majeure Event includes any act, event, non-occurrence, omission or accident beyond our reasonable control and includes, in particular (without limitation), the following: 
      * 8.3.1 strikes, lock-outs or other industrial action; or
      * 8.3.2 civil commotion, riot, invasion, terrorist attack or threat of terrorist attack, war (whether declared or not) or threat or preparation for war; or
      * 8.3.3 fire, explosion, storm, flood, earthquake, volcano, subsidence, epidemic or other natural disaster; or
      * 8.3.4 impossibility of the use of railways, shipping, aircraft, motor transport or other means of public or private transport; or
      * 8.3.5 impossibility of the use of public or private telecommunications networks.
    * 8.4 Our obligations under these Terms are suspended for the period that the Force Majeure Event continues, and we will extend the time to perform these obligations for the duration of that period. We will take reasonable steps to bring the Force Majeure Event to a close or to find a solution by which our obligations under these Terms can be performed despite the Force Majeure Event.
  9. ## Termination

    * 9.1 Either of us may terminate the arrangement between us at any time by providing the other party with 30 calendar days' prior notice in writing.
    * 9.2 Termination will not affect either party's outstanding rights or duties, including our right to recover from you any money you owe us under these Terms
    * 9.3 We will provide the Services for the period according to the Order.
  10. ## Assignment

You may not transfer any of your rights or obligations under these Terms to another person without our prior written consent, which we will not withhold unreasonably. We can transfer all or any of our rights and obligations under these Terms to another organisation, but this will not affect your rights under these Terms.

  11. ## Notices

All notices sent by you to us must be sent to HEADSPACE MEDITATION LIMITED at info@headspace.com . We may give notice to you at either the e-mail or postal address you provide to us in the Order. Notice will be deemed received and properly served 24 hours after an e-mail is sent or three days after the date of posting of any letter. In proving the service of any notice, it will be sufficient to prove, in the case of a letter, that the letter was properly addressed, stamped and placed in the post and, in the case of an e-mail, that the e-mail was sent to the specified e-mail address of the addressee.

  12. ## Data protection

    * 12.1 Save where you expressly consent We will only use the personal information you provide to us to provide the Services, or to inform you about similar services which we provide, unless you tell us that you do not want to receive this information.
  13. ## General

    * 13.1 If any court or competent authority decides that any of the provisions of these Terms are invalid, unlawful or unenforceable to any extent, the term will, to that extent only, be severed from the remaining terms, which will continue to be valid to the fullest extent permitted by law.
    * 13.2 If we fail, at any time while these Terms are in force, to insist that you perform any of your obligations under these Terms, or if we do not exercise any of our rights or remedies under these Terms, that will not mean that we have waived such rights or remedies and will not mean that you do not have to comply with those obligations. If we do waive a default by you ,that will not mean that we will automatically waive any subsequent default by you. No waiver by us of any of these Terms shall be effective unless we expressly say that it is a waiver and we tell you so in writing.
    * 13.3 A person who is not party to these Terms shall not have any rights under or in connection with them under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999.
    * 13.4 These Terms shall be governed by English law and you and we both agree to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.
  14. ## Interpretation

    * 14.1 The definitions in this clause apply to these Terms:

Force Majeure Event: shall have the meaning given in clause 8.  
Order: your order for the Services.  
Order Confirmation: shall have the meaning set out in clause clause 1.4.  
Services: the services that we are providing to you as set out in the Order.  
Terms: the terms and conditions set out in this document.  
We/us: Headspace Mediation Limited.  
Writing or written: includes e-mail.

This acceptable use policy sets out the terms between you and us under which you may access our website www.getsomeheadspace.com (our site). This acceptable use policy applies to all users of, and visitors to, our site.

Your use of our site means that you accept, and agree to abide by, all the policies in this acceptable use policy, which supplement our terms of website use.

[www.getsomeheadspace.com](http://www.getsomeheadspace.com/) is a site operated by Headspace Meditation Limited („We“ or „Us“). We are registered in England and Wales under company number 07094561 and have our registered office at Unit 73, 135 Sherpherdess Walk, London, N1 7RR . Our main trading address is 1 Hamilton Mews, Mayfair, London, W1J 7HA]. Our VAT number is 984592170.

We are a limited company.

## Prohibited uses

You may use our site only for lawful purposes. You may not use our site:

  * In any way that breaches any applicable local, national or international law or regulation.
  * In any way that is unlawful or fraudulent, or has any unlawful or fraudulent purpose or effect.
  * For the purpose of harming or attempting to harm minors in any way.
  * To send, knowingly receive, upload, download, use or re-use any material which does not comply with our content standards.
  * To transmit, or procure the sending of, any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising or promotional material or any other form of similar solicitation (spam).
  * To knowingly transmit any data, send or upload any material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time–bombs, keystroke loggers, spyware, adware or any other harmful programs or similar computer code designed to adversely affect the operation of any computer software or hardware.

You also agree:

  * Not to reproduce, duplicate, copy or re-sell any part of our site in contravention of the provisions of our terms of website use.
  * Not to access without authority, interfere with, damage or disrupt:
  * any part of our site;
  * any equipment or network on which our site is stored;
  * any software used in the provision of our site; or
  * any equipment or network or software owned or used by any third party.

## Interactive services

We may from time to time provide interactive services on our site, including, without limitation:

  * Chat rooms.
  * Bulletin boards.
  * Blog Postings

**(interactive services)**.

Where we do provide any interactive service, we will provide clear information to you about the kind of service offered, if it is moderated and what form of moderation is used (including whether it is human or technical).

We will do our best to assess any possible risks for users (and in particular, for children) from third parties when they use any interactive service provided on our site, and we will decide in each case whether it is appropriate to use moderation of the relevant service (including what kind of moderation to use) in the light of those risks. However, we are under no obligation to oversee, monitor or moderate any interactive service we provide on our site, and we expressly exclude our liability for any loss or damage arising from the use of any interactive service by a user in contravention of our content standards, whether the service is moderated or not.

The use of any of our interactive services by a minor is subject to the consent of their parent or guardian. We advise parents who permit their children to use an interactive service that it is important that they communicate with their children about their safety online, as moderation is not foolproof. Minors who are using any interactive service should be made aware of the potential risks to them.

Where we do moderate an interactive service, we will normally provide you with a means of contacting the moderator, should a concern or difficulty arise.

## Content standards

These content standards apply to any and all material which you contribute to our site (contributions), and to any interactive services associated with it.

You must comply with the spirit of the following standards as well as the letter. The standards apply to each part of any contribution as well as to its whole.

Contributions must:

  * Be accurate (where they state facts).
  * Be genuinely held (where they state opinions).
  * Comply with applicable law in the UK and in any country from which they are posted.

Contributions must not:

  * Contain any material which is defamatory of any person.
  * Contain any material which is obscene, offensive, hateful or inflammatory.
  * Promote sexually explicit material.
  * Promote violence.
  * Promote discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation or age.
  * Infringe any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person.
  * Be likely to deceive any person.
  * Be made in breach of any legal duty owed to a third party, such as a contractual duty or a duty of confidence.
  * Promote any illegal activity.
  * Be threatening, abuse or invade another's privacy, or cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety.
  * Be likely to harass, upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person.
  * Be used to impersonate any person, or to misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person.
  * Give the impression that they emanate from us, if this is not the case.
  * Advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act such as (by way of example only) copyright infringement or computer misuse.

## Suspension and termination

We will determine, in our discretion, whether there has been a breach of this acceptable use policy through your use of our site. When a breach of this policy has occurred, we may take such action as we deem appropriate.

Failure to comply with this acceptable use policy constitutes a material breach of the terms of use upon which you are permitted to use our site, and may result in our taking all or any of the following actions:

  * Immediate, temporary or permanent withdrawal of your right to use our site.
  * Immediate, temporary or permanent removal of any posting or material uploaded by you to our site.
  * Issue of a warning to you.
  * Legal proceedings against you for reimbursement of all costs on an indemnity basis (including, but not limited to, reasonable administrative and legal costs) resulting from the breach.
  * Further legal action against you.
  * Disclosure of such information to law enforcement authorities as we reasonably feel is necessary.

We exclude liability for actions taken in response to breaches of this acceptable use policy. The responses described in this policy are not limited, and we may take any other action we reasonably deem appropriate.

## Changes to the acceptable use policy

We may revise this acceptable use policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are legally binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in this acceptable use policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site.
